Guide to the Leland Stanford Collection SC0512
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Miscellaneous Materials, Series 9
  - The Monarch Philanthropist (San Francisco: Cubery & Company), 1892 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Railroad memorabilia, 1890-1900 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Parlor No. 76, N. S. G. W. - dance card 1892; invitation and program 1900
    - Leland Stanford Div. No. 283, B. of L. E., complimentary pass to fifth annual ball, 1890
  - Correspondence and clippings on "would-be" descendants and other questionable statements, 1893-1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Conger, Allen C. to Sterling, re Stanford's visit to Harvard, 1961
    - Dolph, Cyrus: correspondence with R. L. Wilbur re Stanford's offer to adopt him, 1941, and later press releases, clippings, and memos, 1968
    - Scibird, Ruth: correspondence on Stanford history, 1948-1949
    - Miller, Charles H. to Willie Price, relating a loan he made to Stanford in Wisconsin, 1893
    - Albany County Historical Associaton Record, article on Stanfords, 1948 Feb
    - Assorted clippings, 1953-1962
  - Commemmorative stamps, proposed, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Letterhead from Hotel Stanford, San Francisco, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Note from C. A. Black to J. A. Griffith of Land Commissioner's Office in Omaha
  - Clipping re Leland Stanford's death mask and sculptor Rubert Schmid, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)